(node:42536) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (8.9664ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (4.7586ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (6.4637ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (2.3313ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (2.8354ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (1.0404ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (0.8956ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (0.9735ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (0.8787ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (442.8019ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (49.0501ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (60.4374ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (126.8893ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (41.8185ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (248.1411ms)
ℹ tests 15
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 15
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 2696.8281
