(node:6376) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (12.9307ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (1.6596ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (15.0394ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (3.6106ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (3.0296ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (4.978ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (2.0739ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (101.4939ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (22.768ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (24778.7689ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (1219.9928ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (464.3421ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (2.5049ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (22043.2418ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (525.2079ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (128.1317ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (648.0391ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (14.3893ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (445.0297ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (23986.3493ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (47.6729ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (24304.9463ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (4.616ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (13.9858ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (3.4053ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (3.3445ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (7473.7935ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (4850.2412ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (3261.7405ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (4.2473ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (4359.6992ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (11.6165ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (6.1933ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (5485.9321ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (7.2254ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (4.186ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (10.8905ms)
(node:39104) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (21.6577ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (2.4165ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (0.6485ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (0.6617ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (0.6959ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (3.7845ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (0.7777ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (1.7271ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (0.9558ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (3016.8357ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (442.3955ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (755.4644ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (1235.1615ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (390.1982ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (2342.5447ms)
✔ daily summary uses current challenge, correct owner and lightweight queries (11.7332ms)
✔ tour migration preserves legacy completion and isolates accounts with RLS (19727.5604ms)
✔ tour API refuses unauthorized requests and cannot write another account (52.7517ms)
✔ a completion response cannot alter a tour after an auth or route transition (7.1936ms)
✔ tour receipts and dismissal are per-account, and dismissal never records completion (49.6511ms)
(node:40672) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (12.0492ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (3.5641ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (1.4753ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (3.1787ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (4.8811ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (2.5416ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (4.5034ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (1.0593ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (24.1717ms)
(node:17020) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (38.9771ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (0.8182ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (0.4139ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.4017ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.5826ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (1.2312ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (0.6629ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (0.9117ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (0.6077ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (0.598ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.445ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.2456ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.3152ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.2917ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.3141ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (9.2177ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (2.4338ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.3672ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.8415ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.4476ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (1.2201ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (27.8846ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (15.7342ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (17.2208ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (3.2973ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (1.9219ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (10.4484ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (81.8491ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (18.6684ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (109.6561ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (463.1697ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (22.7135ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (2.2672ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (319.5012ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (1018.8995ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (1.1932ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (1.1884ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (2.597ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (1.8685ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (0.6107ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (8.4093ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (2.4529ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (45.3981ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (3.991ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (1.9015ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (1.8079ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (2.4444ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (7.5904ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (8.2431ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (9.8261ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (19.5449ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (112.2612ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (17.6942ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (4.9341ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (2.0006ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (6.654ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.7088ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (0.8228ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (5.6548ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (2.8988ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (7.857ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (4728.0194ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (4.2845ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (3021.4652ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (43.2936ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (2.6848ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (3.8279ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (3.2623ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (23.9675ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (65.2858ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (617.8023ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (85.2146ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (7.239ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (1.2961ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.0957ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (58.5042ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (6.7268ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.1041ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (34.9024ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (11.0874ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (7.7369ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (68.5135ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (59.2069ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (0.6205ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.2653ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.2363ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.2156ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.1909ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.1755ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (0.3325ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (2.5348ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (14.164ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (9.6527ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (70.3322ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (4.4418ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (3.4244ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (2.3186ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (6.5603ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (585.8292ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (194.0841ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (111.1181ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (116.3459ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (133.6676ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (127.7172ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (5.743ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (93.8294ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (47.8607ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (65.1237ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (241.628ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (30.6319ms)
(node:27120) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (6.1729ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (0.5672ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (4.637ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (0.7137ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (1.2167ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (213.1841ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (85.4183ms)
(node:33008) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (2.5982ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (1.3208ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (202.1347ms)
(node:13012) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (26.5415ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (3.2402ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (2.8654ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (2.2655ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (3.61ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (2.2596ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (0.8055ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (5.3159ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (0.9543ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (3361.2067ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (1924.8596ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (1532.7425ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (1831.89ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (1415.9224ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (1782.5036ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (12.8198ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (1.1093ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (22.4685ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (3.4605ms)
(node:19920) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (15.6476ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (7.1606ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (1.6209ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (1.2386ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (2.4069ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (2.6048ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (84.3475ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (0.8707ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (0.8122ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (0.9716ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.698ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.2708ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (0.2967ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (0.325ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (0.4256ms)
(node:43684) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (16.6601ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (0.9759ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (7.2965ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (1.8837ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (1.5551ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (1.0826ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (82.0648ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (1.1309ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (0.7275ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (1.0165ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (1.7552ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (0.706ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (0.5372ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (2.7051ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (41.676ms)
(node:41032) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (13.5091ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (6.7884ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (3.5036ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (3.485ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (1.5999ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (3.5713ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (110.8231ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (1.8054ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (1.5608ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (5.6017ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (0.8282ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (2.9493ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (0.563ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (0.9847ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (1.1969ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (41.7898ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (1.5179ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (3.1437ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (1.1643ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (1.4104ms)
(node:35792) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (61.3252ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (23.0908ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (22.8754ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (12.4913ms)
(node:14128) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (38.9629ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (8.4952ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (0.6938ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (1.1775ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (1.2443ms)
ℹ tests 264
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 264
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 50501.4484
