(node:39200) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (15.6208ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (5.0912ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (2.7868ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (2.6494ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (2.347ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (2.1154ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (2.4362ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (81.5213ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (4.3284ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (15329.9777ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (580.357ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (174.6707ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (2.3916ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (13768.9506ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (490.6459ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (107.4327ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (208.3729ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (14.7078ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (441.0947ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (14757.4486ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (21.8608ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (14768.3591ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (2.6629ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (11.4641ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (3.2488ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (1.3533ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (5173.2693ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (4703.6372ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (4101.5852ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (5.8114ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (3623.9679ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (6.2699ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (5.0309ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (3553.6727ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (6.1717ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (3.3271ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (6.0918ms)
(node:35928) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (9.0191ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (2.1406ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (0.9729ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (0.7893ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (2.6998ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (4.6154ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (0.6842ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (0.8608ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (0.7607ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (1523.9721ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (306.8301ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (152.1599ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (480.3166ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (367.6929ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (637.2079ms)
✔ daily summary uses current challenge, correct owner and lightweight queries (7.8426ms)
✔ tour migration preserves legacy completion and isolates accounts with RLS (13216.8389ms)
✔ tour API refuses unauthorized requests and cannot write another account (12.9981ms)
✔ a completion response cannot alter a tour after an auth or route transition (8.7326ms)
✔ tour receipts and dismissal are per-account, and dismissal never records completion (7.452ms)
(node:27492) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (12.168ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (3.0182ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (1.6205ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (3.1063ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (1.4409ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (3.1783ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (3.67ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (1.1657ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (28.6306ms)
(node:42464) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (136.2438ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (0.8353ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (0.7176ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.5882ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.9003ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (1.6059ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (0.9754ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (21.0303ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (1.9749ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (0.8601ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.6654ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.6025ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (1.8748ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.9026ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.8673ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (46.3249ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (1.3323ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.355ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.6017ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.5666ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (1.1866ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (0.3828ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.4526ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (0.6882ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (3.1198ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (2.1078ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (15.3624ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (46.2252ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (5.9433ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (67.962ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (117.705ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (10.6362ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (1.5351ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (157.4834ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (731.9198ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (24.5143ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (0.5202ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (0.6085ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (38.7502ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (0.854ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (23.3352ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (35.0447ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (19.7885ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (25.4018ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (3.5215ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (2.3758ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (2.2648ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (2.1919ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (2.5969ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (1.6235ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (16.8453ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (46.2105ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (35.944ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (4.592ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (1.3991ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (67.934ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (1.6388ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (1.4372ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (4.9876ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (4.7749ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (2.5009ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (1590.0614ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (5.9362ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (1749.6812ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (1.1229ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (1.097ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (5.5638ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (3.3505ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (68.0822ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (18.5733ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (351.3349ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (8.3077ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (38.644ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (1.0783ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (12.5845ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (4.7708ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (3.9516ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (7.1551ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (4.2969ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.902ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (9.3101ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (7.6144ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (4.3622ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (0.5149ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.2909ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.2359ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.2308ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.2321ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (15.5563ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (0.8914ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (6.5622ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.3569ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.384ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (5.5398ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (6.8512ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (35.6495ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (4.0348ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (1.5544ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (186.057ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (82.95ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (38.685ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (60.0994ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (34.6404ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (29.6357ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (19.5811ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (14.4713ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (50.0301ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (8.2591ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (200.8581ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (32.919ms)
(node:35864) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (4.4231ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (1.1984ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (15.1721ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (0.6287ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (0.6077ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (49.474ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (2.3648ms)
(node:40024) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (3.3826ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (0.7487ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (33.0587ms)
(node:20448) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (28.3548ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (1.7479ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (0.8329ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (0.8238ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (1.9134ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (1.9315ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (1.3728ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (1.7841ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (2.0139ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (1259.1896ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (856.5051ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (648.3982ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (352.6204ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (415.5543ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (401.8097ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (3.5422ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (0.8164ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (0.7505ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (1.0447ms)
(node:39804) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (9.186ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (1.0502ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (0.7795ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (0.4535ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (0.594ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (1.7272ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (0.5102ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (0.8526ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (0.582ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (0.771ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.5489ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.3452ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (0.3827ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (0.6288ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (4.6444ms)
(node:15876) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (6.7305ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (1.0776ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (5.7114ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (4.6006ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (27.8379ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (1.2969ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (177.1767ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (1.3746ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (1.1328ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (1.2329ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (1.0541ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (2.0457ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (1.8248ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (0.6417ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (96.8479ms)
(node:24364) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (6.6754ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (0.8075ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (5.0809ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (3.0843ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (1.9573ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (2.7076ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (94.5515ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (1.34ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (1.6205ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (9.3283ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (0.703ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (2.1284ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (0.502ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (0.6282ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (7.6912ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (9.3473ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (21.7997ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (1.4206ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (0.8148ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (1.8696ms)
(node:36820) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (44.2591ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (9.1432ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (41.0957ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (12.5192ms)
(node:33756) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (9.7242ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (10.5125ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (29.6681ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (2.2655ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (1.3642ms)
ℹ tests 264
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 264
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 36582.4333
