✔ independent owners cannot release each other; original inline style and priority return (10.2105ms)
✔ reverse cleanup, repeated open/close, and Strict Mode effect replay leave no lock (1.3164ms)
✔ different documents keep independent lock ownership (0.8133ms)
(node:29768) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (12.3969ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (14.6385ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (6.9745ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (1.8686ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (2.3672ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (2.9444ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (3.5016ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (148.3944ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (1.7593ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (26034.5976ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (945.7355ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (162.7434ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (1.4483ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (22785.0696ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (461.2917ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (35.0414ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (227.4105ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (47.1147ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (428.2636ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (25169.8137ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (56.19ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (25311.0027ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (2.3827ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (14.2602ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (3.966ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (2.8209ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (8219.4708ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (4586.0719ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (4267.2408ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (5.2074ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (4905.8647ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (8.0061ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (9.4346ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (5564.9447ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (5.8351ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (4.9065ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (7.9113ms)
(node:24276) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (16.7615ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (3.3796ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (2.5939ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (2.4862ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (3.8835ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (0.5698ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (22.9027ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (28.7222ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (29.8603ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (1512.5838ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (1009.079ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (412.3578ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (1194.2246ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (270.9191ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (1267.8822ms)
✔ daily summary uses current challenge, correct owner and lightweight queries (7.3296ms)
✔ tour migration preserves legacy completion and isolates accounts with RLS (22909.522ms)
✔ tour API refuses unauthorized requests and cannot write another account (31.0145ms)
✔ a completion response cannot alter a tour after an auth or route transition (14.5955ms)
✔ tour receipts and dismissal are per-account, and dismissal never records completion (27.7641ms)
(node:21696) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (30.5246ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (12.8805ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (4.7321ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (4.4988ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (1.412ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (3.1116ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (7.18ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (1.6724ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (14.3226ms)
(node:36740) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (37.2485ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (0.9148ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (0.3303ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.3104ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.4097ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (0.9089ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (0.2912ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (0.3041ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (0.5783ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (0.5872ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.3185ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.2367ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.2051ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.2094ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.1788ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (18.2964ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (1.7616ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.3985ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.5544ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.4579ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (0.2502ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (0.5423ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.3976ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (1.7261ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (3.2698ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (4.0727ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (100.8885ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (16.9864ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (59.3706ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (46.1489ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (110.1162ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (19.8397ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (2.5886ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (345.6026ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (1908.0217ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (14.5813ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (14.416ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (24.4243ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (68.9434ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (0.908ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (29.7888ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (3.4352ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (69.2018ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (11.5671ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (2.6532ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (7.2053ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (6.9776ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (7.574ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (2.1112ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (2.3836ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (12.2922ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (34.7076ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (51.0691ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (5.1373ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (3.834ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (379.644ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.6657ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (9.2138ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (16.4337ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (5.1846ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (2.3579ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (2996.003ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (9.3955ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (6156.7858ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (40.6237ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (13.338ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (23.2743ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (42.3007ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (55.637ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (219.366ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (1700.1193ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (51.0022ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (25.9468ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (1.2116ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (37.1928ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (26.4214ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (4.8113ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (26.3607ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (30.1037ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (27.41ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (35.8779ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (41.5176ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (17.6037ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (3.1126ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.4647ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.2798ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.2166ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.2257ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.2122ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (3.2315ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (2.9629ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.1382ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (23.524ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (17.0387ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (9.6418ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (1.2976ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (20.559ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (16.5592ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (352.9067ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (44.1245ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (243.6645ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (79.8794ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (42.1176ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (48.0276ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (37.3232ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (42.2929ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (51.2326ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (11.1915ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (375.6256ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (16.5553ms)
(node:40276) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (3.3607ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (0.7352ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (3.7627ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (0.5438ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (0.5642ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (80.2383ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (5.3488ms)
(node:36248) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (8.2045ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (0.8059ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (38.8211ms)
(node:24656) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (6.4854ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (1.0324ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (0.5318ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (16.2218ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (0.9487ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (28.2252ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (0.6709ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (3.5212ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (0.8624ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (2449.1847ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (1040.3249ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (540.7947ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (451.5151ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (398.9822ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (382.7007ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (12.9833ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (2.4417ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (2.6779ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (2.194ms)
(node:7968) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (4.5966ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (23.9417ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (3.7044ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (0.4128ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (0.4931ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (1.2577ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (0.5598ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (1.0723ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (1.3428ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (0.8725ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.4238ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.2616ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (22.5009ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (0.4234ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (0.5116ms)
(node:43708) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (5.8211ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (0.8835ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (2.917ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (3.8741ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (20.9766ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (4.133ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (81.851ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (3.8423ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (1.2574ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (1.418ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (1.6858ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (0.7098ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (1.0628ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (0.6291ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (213.8243ms)
(node:39916) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (15.9397ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (0.5685ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (7.0405ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (1.2162ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (1.7221ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (1.5624ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (95.363ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (1.5477ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (1.0146ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (7.2132ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (0.6892ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (29.1303ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (4.6557ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (0.6674ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (1.1022ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (7.5795ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (1.5583ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (0.8354ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (0.3863ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (0.5525ms)
(node:41208) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (84.0705ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (7.0426ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (11.2398ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (4.6701ms)
(node:34968) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (28.8897ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (5.6719ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (0.44ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (3.0421ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (1.7595ms)
ℹ tests 267
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 267
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 53882.5614
