✔ independent owners cannot release each other; original inline style and priority return (5.3845ms)
✔ reverse cleanup, repeated open/close, and Strict Mode effect replay leave no lock (0.9973ms)
✔ different documents keep independent lock ownership (0.7254ms)
(node:39460) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (12.0281ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (2.9215ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (3.3517ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (2.3416ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (2.4529ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (3.3839ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (3.1074ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (109.2835ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (7.5621ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (27282.4543ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (691.9949ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (138.4273ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (1.5344ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (24923.0706ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (765.7516ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (166.6972ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (198.3135ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (13.4567ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (552.4902ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (25716.4805ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (44.86ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (26103.5314ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (2.4851ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (12.2586ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (3.2331ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (2.8392ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (5825.5238ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (3962.7572ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (3851.9649ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (5.4818ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (3594.4842ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (8.2509ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (5.525ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (3479.6362ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (8.0985ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (2.835ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (3.2947ms)
(node:42268) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (15.2196ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (9.5798ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (1.4964ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (1.8626ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (2.3503ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (36.8589ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (1.0001ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (1.3676ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (0.8582ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (3623.8478ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (893.0388ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (1198.0859ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (3400.5661ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (1607.1382ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (5579.7595ms)
✔ daily summary uses current challenge, correct owner and lightweight queries (15.9281ms)
✔ tour migration preserves legacy completion and isolates accounts with RLS (24477.676ms)
✔ tour API refuses unauthorized requests and cannot write another account (23.7668ms)
✔ a completion response cannot alter a tour after an auth or route transition (12.5117ms)
✔ tour receipts and dismissal are per-account, and dismissal never records completion (16.3933ms)
(node:37136) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (21.8504ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (6.2593ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (1.9693ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (16.2689ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (4.0928ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (3.2261ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (3.6216ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (1.0864ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (34.8124ms)
(node:23676) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (19.4479ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (3.5039ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (1.3731ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.5732ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (1.607ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (7.5296ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (110.9769ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (0.5925ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (49.0816ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (49.5919ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (1.7917ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.3279ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.2368ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.2856ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.2111ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (10.7794ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (1.4631ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.5248ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.714ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.4781ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (0.8136ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (3.7349ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.4279ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (59.2762ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (6.6764ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (2.3339ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (14.5438ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (9.7378ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (6.7034ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (130.0119ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (442.8245ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (12.1099ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (2.7564ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (499.2906ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (1264.3552ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (32.641ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (6.1945ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (1.1111ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (9.2091ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (4.3295ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (34.2606ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (3.8348ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (116.24ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (8.9636ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (1.2983ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (2.3984ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (45.8897ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (6.1871ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (10.84ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (1.2726ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (4.9757ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (75.5939ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (49.1103ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (32.7909ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (1.6894ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (63.3415ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.8932ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (1.063ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (3.0878ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (3.7249ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (2.3062ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (8823.3338ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (23.3978ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (4816.1111ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (12.0067ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (22.588ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (12.6184ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (4.9246ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (11.7582ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (50.5721ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (347.9695ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (9.1778ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (22.7524ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (1.1181ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.5966ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (3.8715ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (11.348ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.4108ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (7.8128ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (14.532ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (11.9113ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (8.9482ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (14.3652ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (16.1654ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (5.95ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.3747ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.831ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.2735ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.3728ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (23.3547ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (13.823ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.938ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.9439ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.6773ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (2.7185ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (1.9019ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (5.4954ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (2.4524ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (143.4014ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (67.7589ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (34.2569ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (24.073ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (32.375ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (34.4357ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (1.691ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (6.2591ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (63.2203ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (2.333ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (137.1818ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (8.1899ms)
(node:38032) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (2.951ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (0.5109ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (18.1446ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (1.0472ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (1.5847ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (119.6756ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (9.2803ms)
(node:25808) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (3.6657ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (0.7573ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (59.1451ms)
(node:9392) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (87.5545ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (1.0516ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (0.6431ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (1.492ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (0.999ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (0.8585ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (0.6746ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (2.636ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (3.1407ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (3012.8508ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (2423.0104ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (2344.4116ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (3297.4245ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (2848.9504ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (1680.3553ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (3.1505ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (0.7896ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (0.7944ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (1.558ms)
(node:39088) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (22.1013ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (1.0151ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (0.511ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (0.7263ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (1.0788ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (1.6566ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (1.686ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (0.8294ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (108.4131ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (7.4223ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.5223ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.3211ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (0.4344ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (0.4511ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (40.7613ms)
(node:41376) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (12.2818ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (4.2915ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (5.4569ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (2.937ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (1.1728ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (2.0399ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (143.4289ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (1.3237ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (0.9201ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (57.5309ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (1.439ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (1.0906ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (0.7996ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (1.3466ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (56.45ms)
(node:22140) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (9.865ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (1.5545ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (8.2532ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (3.7194ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (1.0634ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (1.6144ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (187.0172ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (1.7569ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (47.7691ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (22.9976ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (0.766ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (2.344ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (1.1033ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (1.9625ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (1.4433ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (68.2604ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (1.3085ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (1.7113ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (1.0637ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (1.0705ms)
(node:12376) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (115.751ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (10.2682ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (239.9748ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (25.2449ms)
(node:43860) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (50.0137ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (89.7955ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (1.0871ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (6.2446ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (2.0887ms)
ℹ tests 267
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 267
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 47781.0966
