✔ independent owners cannot release each other; original inline style and priority return (3.7872ms)
✔ reverse cleanup, repeated open/close, and Strict Mode effect replay leave no lock (0.8635ms)
✔ different documents keep independent lock ownership (0.4789ms)
(node:39568) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (21.3157ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (1.563ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (1.8205ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (1.8156ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (1.8654ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (1.9476ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (2.1946ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (287.0627ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (2.3787ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (13929.1619ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (539.7737ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (58.0199ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (1.3352ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (12588.3568ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (254.8992ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (37.8391ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (125.435ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (11.0345ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (265.3048ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (14029.2467ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (39.3722ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (12942.2122ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (3.8538ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (12.1752ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (3.8826ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (2.9371ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (5799.9991ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (4366.158ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (3612.6448ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (4.7694ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (3719.7794ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (9.1531ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (6.6235ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (3757.6042ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (8.431ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (2.8211ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (4.9925ms)
(node:31148) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (28.0315ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (5.1425ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (0.8539ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (1.3732ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (1.2484ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (0.6552ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (0.843ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (5.5305ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (3.1431ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (1839.1943ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (175.4774ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (147.5295ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (1074.2442ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (412.9401ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (959.1967ms)
✔ daily summary uses current challenge, correct owner and lightweight queries (7.579ms)
✔ tour migration preserves legacy completion and isolates accounts with RLS (11725.8574ms)
✔ tour API refuses unauthorized requests and cannot write another account (9.7151ms)
✔ a completion response cannot alter a tour after an auth or route transition (4.7815ms)
✔ tour receipts and dismissal are per-account, and dismissal never records completion (8.5043ms)
(node:30168) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (12.458ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (4.5318ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (1.9015ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (4.6774ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (3.0424ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (13.6022ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (2.4333ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (0.8169ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (15.7487ms)
(node:23228) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (7.2844ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (1.1352ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (0.4868ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.3551ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.4773ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (0.876ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (0.3265ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (0.3909ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (0.3853ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (0.6413ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.5182ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.3585ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.1949ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.2209ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.6873ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (5.4218ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (2.2968ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.3132ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.5055ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.5104ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (0.8636ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (0.381ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.6508ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (0.695ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (3.7985ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (2.2074ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (9.8344ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (23.6471ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (18.873ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (59.4308ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (162.3878ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (11.2212ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (1.4338ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (127.6086ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (491.7908ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (1.5966ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (0.9336ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (0.7802ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (6.6362ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (0.7349ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (5.816ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (2.9878ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (16.2245ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (6.3041ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (1.3938ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (2.1103ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (2.4819ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (6.3398ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (2.7609ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (0.9172ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (6.7301ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (83.3778ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (16.702ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (15.0396ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (7.4546ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (22.4435ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.7697ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (1.0975ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (2.5655ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (3.0901ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (6.373ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (1858.6983ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (2.6279ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (1192.0989ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (18.6618ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (6.5293ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (65.9106ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (21.4018ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (54.6354ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (80.7752ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (377.7497ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (53.4569ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (7.7752ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (1.1996ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (39.6061ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (3.6977ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.5005ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (6.4041ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.8797ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (38.9935ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (6.092ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (48.7563ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (5.0074ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (31.557ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.6817ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.2387ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.2211ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.196ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.2256ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (0.3817ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (6.241ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.4458ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.308ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (2.383ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (5.7648ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (2.194ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (29.0052ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (3.1754ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (84.1052ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (85.046ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (89.6508ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (32.0195ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (24.3744ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (47.3555ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (3.3542ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (8.3022ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (81.9086ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (2.2884ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (273.8827ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (46.3387ms)
(node:30776) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (3.197ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (0.9004ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (4.1151ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (1.1105ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (0.8877ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (43.7591ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (2.2777ms)
(node:43680) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (2.8256ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (0.7299ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (26.5529ms)
(node:25860) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (4.4469ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (0.9894ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (2.1397ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (1.873ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (1.4225ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (0.7577ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (0.4481ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (0.8119ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (0.474ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (1396.5879ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (491.5307ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (368.3525ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (837.9114ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (655.1411ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (954.6946ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (3.3375ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (0.9286ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (0.7189ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (0.9675ms)
(node:27148) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (13.7774ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (0.925ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (0.4667ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (0.3567ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (0.4721ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (1.5165ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (0.7282ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (0.6616ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (11.1528ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (1.2353ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.5647ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.4473ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (0.5065ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (0.3753ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (0.4785ms)
(node:38720) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (5.4304ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (0.9782ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (2.3468ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (1.7926ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (0.7369ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (1.3738ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (98.5366ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (1.347ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (1.2765ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (1.1332ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (0.8908ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (0.5516ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (0.8135ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (0.6874ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (88.8877ms)
(node:23400) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (5.901ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (0.6548ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (1.8857ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (1.1453ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (0.7285ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (1.2436ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (53.7122ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (1.532ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (1.1861ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (7.505ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (0.9267ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (2.0938ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (0.5664ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (1.1819ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (1.6088ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (5.0442ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (1.0216ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (0.9732ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (0.5564ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (0.7654ms)
(node:36360) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (74.0804ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (17.3578ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (10.9067ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (3.6815ms)
(node:15404) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (106.976ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (8.5981ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (0.4724ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (1.457ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (1.0961ms)
ℹ tests 267
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 267
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 34832.8051
