(node:27768) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (15.0784ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (3.5572ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (1.3575ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (1.3369ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (0.8834ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (0.6681ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (0.6902ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (0.614ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (4.0797ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (540.6774ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (62.7896ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (45.819ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (135.3494ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (52.3363ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (294.6831ms)
(node:36496) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (11.4581ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (0.7022ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (0.3751ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.3292ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.4591ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (0.5763ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (0.2216ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (0.4008ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (0.9338ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (1.6308ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.5402ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.3816ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.1546ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.2126ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.2422ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (6.3814ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (0.7938ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.1851ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.3385ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.2519ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (0.147ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (0.3825ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.2758ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (0.6291ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (2.2257ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (2.6702ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (8.7397ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (8.7712ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (3.4482ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (27.3927ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (85.2537ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (9.2905ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (2.0983ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (85.3491ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (279.857ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (1.32ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (1.9933ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (1.3364ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (1.6466ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (0.6867ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (6.4756ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (2.8699ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (12.4527ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (3.9566ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (1.3354ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (1.9689ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (2.6387ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (2.1917ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (4.6559ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (1.2054ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (3.9167ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (20.1573ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (17.1554ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (2.7661ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (2.1919ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (1.2886ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.7223ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (1.6383ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (7.388ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (7.4208ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (2.1431ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (513.5538ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (0.7966ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (111.1237ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (0.7771ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (1.3774ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (2.1862ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (1.5476ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (2.871ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (11.5921ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (64.6649ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (3.4676ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (2.8121ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (0.97ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (3.0872ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (1.3345ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (1.7144ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.9825ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.5967ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (1.6962ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.1933ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.2485ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (1.2523ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (0.2415ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.1675ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.1689ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.1911ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.2218ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.1533ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (0.3267ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (2.3934ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.3718ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.416ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.7357ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (1.8503ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (1.621ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (2.2575ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (1.4468ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (28.6973ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (12.4159ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (46.2983ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (26.1578ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (30.5306ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (29.938ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (2.9012ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (4.8299ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (50.6808ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (3.7047ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (50.2457ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (1.3444ms)
ℹ tests 125
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 125
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 3245.2001
