(node:11736) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (31.5441ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (2.4494ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (3.9646ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (2.7821ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (3.5196ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (4.9525ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (10.818ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (553.1195ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (4.8342ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (29269.5582ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (985.6599ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (400.1753ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (1.8913ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (24878.5564ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (763.0491ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (120.9183ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (536.756ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (20.1789ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (702.7953ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (28096.3688ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (106.6843ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (27716.0064ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (14.094ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (97.7997ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (11.3261ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (9.5835ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (9985.2793ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (4951.4333ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (3933.276ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (5.1314ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (4029.2106ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (5.3726ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (39.3774ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (3638.2585ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (7.3437ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (2.7284ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (5.0961ms)
(node:30804) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (121.1243ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (46.8867ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (17.5195ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (17.8063ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (32.5449ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (20.389ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (25.6961ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (25.5518ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (1.4229ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (2776.6081ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (479.0568ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (214.8837ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (1650.1575ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (458.4603ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (798.8602ms)
(node:36972) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (31.3966ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (4.047ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (27.9965ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (28.5812ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (2.8268ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (7.7945ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (30.9855ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (2.6135ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (61.8349ms)
(node:30228) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (90.8487ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (5.1821ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (3.217ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (2.5516ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.6707ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (10.6181ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (1.6117ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (9.3861ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (12.0692ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (8.5208ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.6209ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.394ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.7389ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (1.0136ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.3311ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (44.0999ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (12.2243ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (1.0238ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (3.9425ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (0.7592ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (0.5044ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (0.8629ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.5279ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (15.1353ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (2.4819ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (17.2563ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (145.925ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (65.6559ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (19.4731ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (109.8339ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (392.2983ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (40.0056ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (2.2894ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (469.3187ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (1877.8991ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (2.0982ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (1.2112ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (1.0237ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (17.1578ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (0.9234ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (29.8736ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (7.6613ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (35.6686ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (9.7953ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (1.6075ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (5.0411ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (8.2469ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (2.5351ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (7.2981ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (1.6661ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (15.3333ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (41.3248ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (28.343ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (5.2979ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (1.3582ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (9.8948ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.9037ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (6.0625ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (10.951ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (7.4679ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (9.551ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (1945.3686ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (3.3888ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (3273.6997ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (38.6149ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (10.6252ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (22.6112ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (52.2255ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (51.1979ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (61.9183ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (1472.3099ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (28.1865ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (109.3451ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (2.8669ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (21.2954ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (4.6088ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (120.1077ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (80.0437ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (4.8117ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (12.8874ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.3421ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (9.9088ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (3.6458ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (0.5809ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.3206ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.4935ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.486ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (73.0066ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.4756ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (0.6635ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (6.2463ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.6932ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (2.0199ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (3.4023ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (5.2997ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (4.686ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (6.398ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (2.4722ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (355.1846ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (665.4621ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (225.3171ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (202.1605ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (212.9988ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (149.2981ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (3.3104ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (90.2963ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (145.8855ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (4.6545ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (452.6759ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (47.4595ms)
(node:41176) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (6.498ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (0.5437ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (5.4813ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (1.6666ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (0.9632ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (93.9347ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (82.0011ms)
(node:38000) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (7.2429ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (1.1805ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (47.7538ms)
(node:35596) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (27.2769ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (1.2746ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (5.21ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (0.7444ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (5.473ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (1.2263ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (2.7238ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (6.2536ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (0.66ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (2512.1273ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (3292.2835ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (334.5878ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (420.5164ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (604.2237ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (1288.6942ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (49.3687ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (6.8441ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (4.3719ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (1.564ms)
(node:20856) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (13.0066ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (1.7542ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (0.623ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (1.0025ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (0.9455ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (1.6636ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (0.6366ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (4.2747ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (1.2184ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (1.0496ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.7748ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.6102ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (0.8735ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (0.4843ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (0.691ms)
(node:27192) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (24.5362ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (1.8745ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (3.863ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (2.0818ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (1.0875ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (1.7755ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (487.9694ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (1.9123ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (1.2317ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (1.683ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (1.3727ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (0.6956ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (0.8855ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (0.8238ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (357.4321ms)
(node:21780) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (47.7685ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (0.7517ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (3.064ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (2.3333ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (1.2338ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (2.4085ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (127.2957ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (55.3585ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (1.3788ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (13.1539ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (2.7784ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (4.1241ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (0.8613ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (0.8974ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (1.5829ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (5.7711ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (1.2285ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (1.1147ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (0.608ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (0.9312ms)
(node:42924) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (199.4131ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (42.4952ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (79.1317ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (33.6115ms)
(node:39940) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (37.1275ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (88.6104ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (0.7502ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (4.2743ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (1.6651ms)
(node:7112) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/weeklyRcCompetition.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ ranks descending by the sum of stored composite scores (3.3808ms)
✔ weekly composite total represents multiple stored Daily RC attempts (0.7045ms)
✔ stored time-sensitive composites distinguish equal raw CAT scores (0.5186ms)
✔ uses Monday-to-Sunday boundaries in Asia/Kolkata (147.7788ms)
✔ finalized previous-week snapshots remain immutable (4.1675ms)
ℹ tests 264
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 264
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 55498.7372
