(node:42440) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/entitlement.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-01 (51.6675ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-05 (4.9227ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-10-25 (2.6056ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-19 (4.2143ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-20 (2.1453ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2026-11-29 (2.7512ms)
✔ fixed calendar 2027-01-31 (2.9603ms)
✔ one mapping, ten buffer dates, India midnight boundaries, no invented CAT countdown (701.4504ms)
✔ existing entitlement rules: active trial, purchase, institute, expiry, and no invented extension (6.3417ms)
✔ SQL/service: late join, gaps, arbitrary backlog, official result, partial resume and route locks (23456.3624ms)
✔ ten-day aggregate preserves missing/partial days, weighted counts, samples and privacy (1327.2614ms)
✔ empty, unanswered, missing timing, catch-up dates and Day 50 are truthful (110.3282ms)
✔ development date is strict and ignored outside development (1.8807ms)
✔ analytics endpoint reads only owned Boot Camp data without writes, authentication or keys leaking (22041.6034ms)
✔ generic history handles Day 1, 2, 3, 10, 25 and 50 without future contamination (409.0404ms)
✔ recent windows are completed days, non-overlapping and preserve sample sizes (30.131ms)
✔ improving, persistent and emerging evidence changes focus; one-day samples never diagnose (180.0049ms)
✔ unanswered, partial and explicitly abandoned records are participation, not cognitive mistakes (60.6837ms)
✔ raw correction changes revision and briefing; fifty-day prompt excludes old source text and remains bounded (500.0194ms)
✔ SQL migration: complete Day 1 -> Day 2 -> Day 3; fresh history, ownership, resume and sequencing (24081.647ms)
✔ trap evidence counts selected distractors, and unanswered days do not satisfy trend evidence (43.4915ms)
✔ review loads without coaching; one Continue atomically advances each block and rejects duplicate clicks (22801.8904ms)
✔ missing, empty or wrong-block review data produces an explicit recoverable error (4.8248ms)
✔ source contract: enriched only, exact composition, stable links, typed positions and analysis agreement (12.8035ms)
✔ all five outcomes: timeout keeps saved answers; unseen and presented remain distinct (3.038ms)
✔ public projection never includes answers, source keys, enrichment or future question text (2.1726ms)
✔ SQL + services: full Day 1, resume, immutable snapshot, revisions, ownership, review gates and no legacy writes (9167.952ms)
✔ SQL deadline enforcement, atomic timeout and duplicate finish (6078.5741ms)
✔ browser roles cannot read protected tables or execute privileged functions; API requires authentication (5249.3049ms)
✔ coaching uses only completed performance and rejects ungrounded evidence IDs (4.9815ms)
✔ concurrent saves serialize; repeated start/finish cannot reset time or double-score (4924.9293ms)
✔ Daily RC review adapter preserves authored meaning, evidence, outcomes and display-only answer conversion (10.2085ms)
✔ calendar derives exactly 50 training dates and Monday-first placement from start date (7.7016ms)
✔ contextual chat authenticates ownership, rejects unfinished blocks, is read-only and never uses legacy history (4920.3493ms)
✔ chat history is bounded and summarizes prior mistakes and timing without full old passages (11.346ms)
✔ selected-question chat uses server evidence and rejects questions outside the completed block (4.362ms)
✔ completed report analytics reconcile all outcomes and whole-day trainer context stays server-side (5.259ms)
(node:29676) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/dailyRc/review.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ 2024 A, older B and current attempts retain exact passages, question IDs, answers and explanations (12.0699ms)
✔ another user's attempt is rejected before fetching any passage or answers (5.1391ms)
✔ missing attempt IDs never fall back to today's or latest RC (1.1771ms)
✔ later additions to a set are not substituted for the persisted question set (1.1042ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: wrong-set (1.154ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-question (0.722ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-passage (0.5547ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: missing-response (1.8369ms)
✔ incomplete or inconsistent historical data fails closed: changed-key (25.2114ms)
✔ today's completed report link receives and retains its own attempt ID (2720.8419ms)
✔ review API uses authenticated identity and disables caching (531.6427ms)
✔ client route changes hide old data, abort stale responses and ignore localStorage (442.3151ms)
✔ submission and all review entry points retain attempt identity (1220.463ms)
✔ historical and new result routes share the compact report and preserve the requested attempt (811.6424ms)
✔ compact report retains saved stats and expands review content inside the same shell (1582.8258ms)
✔ daily summary uses current challenge, correct owner and lightweight queries (8.0573ms)
✔ tour migration preserves legacy completion and isolates accounts with RLS (21039.2189ms)
✔ tour API refuses unauthorized requests and cannot write another account (17.9684ms)
✔ a completion response cannot alter a tour after an auth or route transition (8.4197ms)
✔ tour receipts and dismissal are per-account, and dismissal never records completion (58.6508ms)
(node:33364) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/rules.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ real activity selects study over generic progress and respects weakness thresholds (29.123ms)
✔ performance update is the final activity fallback without a volume threshold or cooldown (5.765ms)
✔ stronger rules still win before the restored performance fallback (50.5354ms)
✔ recommendation follow-up and CAT exam prep require saved recommendation or exam weakness (14.0353ms)
✔ perfect session milestone needs ten correct questions (2.3291ms)
✔ trial and account lifecycle use real expiry and subscription rows (2.0512ms)
✔ offer requires expired trial, no active entitlement and a real active coupon (21.6758ms)
✔ announcements require active, targeted, explicitly configured records (1.2109ms)
✔ daily cap and duplicate keys do not suppress transactional notices (29.3151ms)
(node:30776) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/inbox/service.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ internal CTA allows / (56.0251ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /inbox (0.6915ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /?view=precision (0.3867ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /daily-challenge (0.3258ms)
✔ internal CTA allows /history?search=hello%20world#results (0.7602ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "https://evil.test" (0.8493ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "//evil.test" (0.2862ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\\evil.test" (0.3146ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%5cevil.test" (1.0683ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%2fevil.test" (0.5416ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/%252fevil.test" (0.3433ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/\nevil.test" (0.4182ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "javascript:alert(1)" (0.8266ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad%XX" (0.3149ms)
✔ internal CTA rejects "/bad path" (0.2464ms)
✔ notification payload validates user, priority, daily date and retains metadata (133.414ms)
✔ list rejects {"filter":"UNKNOWN"} (1.2004ms)
✔ list rejects {"folder":"OTHER"} (0.3077ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"1.5"} (0.4952ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"Infinity"} (48.536ms)
✔ list rejects {"pageSize":"51"} (1.459ms)
✔ list rejects {"page":"1"} (9.8951ms)
✔ list rejects {"search":"xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx"} (0.9048ms)
✔ list rejects {"cursor":"bad"} (11.7938ms)
✔ cursor is scoped, validated and deterministic (14.2576ms)
✔ bulk validation never silently truncates (3.3056ms)
✔ list enforces ownership, folders, categories, search and deterministic order (113.1488ms)
✔ keyset pagination survives deletion, archiving and a new higher priority message (8.1211ms)
✔ read/unread, archive/unarchive and delete/restore preserve content and actual state (8.5612ms)
✔ bulk operation processes all 250 IDs and does not mutate another user (61.0714ms)
✔ mark all read batches all owned Inbox messages and excludes archive/trash (200.5334ms)
✔ partial bulk failure returns only saved rows and the true count (32.5865ms)
✔ detail GET is read-only and ownership protected, including Trash (1.24ms)
✔ actual handler returns 401/400/404/500 and uses authenticated identity (461.6733ms)
✔ existing authentication validates token and requires a real profile (1117.2547ms)
✔ unread filter and detail reconcile actual partial results (39.5374ms)
✔ mark unread and restoration use folder-aware state (1.4761ms)
✔ stale and cancelled requests cannot overwrite newer state (0.9304ms)
✔ cron authentication fails closed and accepts only the exact secret (2.3753ms)
✔ IST calendar handles midnight and month/year rollover (5.1674ms)
✔ batched activity excludes other users, incomplete sessions and adjacent IST days (75.3312ms)
✔ source failure is not interpreted as inactivity (3.8065ms)
✔ activity pagination reads beyond a server page (46.461ms)
✔ daily performance uses yesterday only and real weighted metrics (11.9625ms)
✔ engagement does not fabricate completed sessions, accuracy or timing (1.3487ms)
✔ progress needs two adequate samples and at least five percentage points (6.8948ms)
✔ recommendation uses measured weak module/skill and seven day cooldown (4.6071ms)
✔ inactivity requires seven days and does not repeat for fourteen days (2.2341ms)
✔ streak requires actual consecutive completed learning days (3.0614ms)
✔ achievement is a real daily threshold, not a fictional lifetime total (1.3487ms)
✔ daily idempotency, cross-rule cap and additional account messages (117.7616ms)
✔ generator batches users, isolates a user failure, logs partial failure and safely retries (145.0066ms)
✔ generator paginates profiles and skips activity queries for already-generated users (19.6143ms)
✔ generator records an activity failure without creating fabricated reminders (8.0899ms)
✔ generator timeout is visible and recorded (105.8574ms)
✔ migration explicitly closes direct UPDATE and declares database-enforced caps (3.7065ms)
✔ CTA rejects normalized protocol-relative paths and API destinations (0.7877ms)
✔ read preserves an existing timestamp and returns current state for a no-op (1.4915ms)
✔ malformed question metrics cannot become performance or a completed streak day (2.8088ms)
✔ RC question submission times supply real skill metrics without counting sessions twice (3.3848ms)
✔ concurrent generators cannot create two proactive messages on the same day (1.5698ms)
✔ Inbox JSX parses and real components render rows, selection, folders and safe metrics (4009.0504ms)
✔ recommendations respect existing exam capabilities (1.8205ms)
✔ Supabase client serializes the actual PostgREST search and cursor contract (2109.2107ms)
✔ migration trigger body has matching dollar-quote delimiters (13.4818ms)
✔ activity today suppresses a false inactivity reminder and stale recommendation (1.5979ms)
✔ generator activity window includes today's return but excludes timestamps after the run (96.6031ms)
✔ ordinary RC without analytics is retained while detailed sessions are not double-counted (11.3931ms)
✔ paginated reads stop before another page after cancellation (11.5245ms)
✔ paginated reads propagate cancellation to an in-flight request (36.3507ms)
✔ generator cancels a slow activity read and still finishes the ledger (695.9241ms)
✔ history failure skips its batch and does not stop subsequent users (6.6837ms)
✔ bulk deadline returns acknowledged writes without inventing missing IDs or a count (216.9263ms)
✔ bulk reconciliation failure preserves confirmed writes and reports incomplete (1.4482ms)
✔ streak milestone at 7 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (106.1233ms)
✔ streak milestone at 14 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.3751ms)
✔ streak milestone at 28 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (4.4396ms)
✔ streak milestone at 29 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (3.2815ms)
✔ streak milestone at 30 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (2.4174ms)
✔ streak milestone at 56 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (5.9813ms)
✔ streak milestone at 57 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (3.7061ms)
✔ streak milestone at 90 days uses an exact threshold, including a bounded history (7.5193ms)
✔ streaks reset after a gap and preserve daily uniqueness (4.2863ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi/inbox/generate (3.1375ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5fnext/static/x (0.2834ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /a/../%61pi/inbox (0.2043ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%61pi%2finbox (0.2179ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%5Fnext (0.4371ms)
✔ encoded excluded CTA rejects /%2561pi/inbox (0.1947ms)
✔ decoded CTA validation keeps search query and hash data legitimate (2.617ms)
✔ explicit read can undo only acknowledged messages (4.2108ms)
✔ explicit unread can undo only acknowledged messages (1.7332ms)
✔ explicit archive can undo only acknowledged messages (4.0631ms)
✔ explicit unarchive can undo only acknowledged messages (1.5422ms)
✔ explicit delete can undo only acknowledged messages (1.9236ms)
✔ explicit restore can undo only acknowledged messages (4.5511ms)
✔ undo skips later changes in another tab and excludes unsafe scopes (3.3983ms)
✔ archive/unarchive no-ops cannot become undo candidates (86.7171ms)
✔ request deadline settles even when an underlying operation ignores cancellation (185.3397ms)
✔ Inbox session wait is bounded (183.5793ms)
✔ Inbox fetch wait is bounded (98.4588ms)
✔ Inbox body wait is bounded (82.181ms)
✔ Inbox mutation wait is bounded (157.846ms)
✔ Inbox unread-count wait is bounded (110.4927ms)
✔ bounded API preserves authorization, cancellation, errors and successful JSON (5.0261ms)
✔ generator loads the 29th day and prevents rolling 28-day notifications (10.8415ms)
✔ generator closes timed-out history reads even when the database ignores abort (183.1998ms)
✔ generator recovers killed runs, preserves live runs and retries ledger finalization (73.7958ms)
✔ navigation moves Inbox to the labeled header control without replacing other items (229.8282ms)
✔ production catalog checks remain a read-only SQL assertion script (96.7514ms)
(node:38160) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 100 rupees to 80 and commissions 20 from original (6.0101ms)
✔ dynamic influencer coupon discounts 1000 rupees to 800 and commissions 200 from original (0.6202ms)
✔ AZADI50 remains a 50 percent coupon (5.9085ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 discounts plan prices by exactly 30 percent (0.7575ms)
✔ dynamic coupon plan pricing uses the shared coupon calculation (0.6318ms)
✔ successful conversion persistence and email are idempotent by payment (36.8336ms)
✔ influencer lookup maps the production name column (5.1977ms)
(node:39052) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/mobile/request.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ discovery respects exam eligibility and disabled products (3.0028ms)
✔ next action skips unavailable and completed work, then offers review (1.1445ms)
✔ requests recover from timeout and respect a caller cancellation signal (31.2298ms)
(node:29896) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/payments/pricing.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ normal purchases retain every existing base price (62.3537ms)
✔ AZADI50 is case-insensitive and applies exactly fifty percent (1.028ms)
✔ invalid coupon is rejected and cannot alter normal pricing (3.1968ms)
✔ existing referral prices remain unchanged (0.6362ms)
✔ coupon takes precedence over referral without stacking (0.7488ms)
✔ order creation uses server pricing rather than a browser amount (0.7301ms)
✔ verification uses authoritative Razorpay order metadata and amount (0.4251ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 has one authoritative 30 percent definition, even with a supplied 20 percent coupon (1.241ms)
✔ other built-in coupons cannot be shadowed either (0.7748ms)
✔ database AUCTOR30 collision is ignored by lookup and validation (2445.4808ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 order and verification agree on 90930 and fulfill the six-month purchase (1478.2461ms)
✔ AUCTOR30 verification cannot accept the colliding 103920 price (956.6557ms)
✔ coupon input cannot reinterpret a six-month order as another plan (1119.5581ms)
✔ legitimate influencer coupon retains validation, pricing, fulfillment and attribution (1448.8156ms)
✔ server-validated referral pricing is also identical at creation and verification (1424.2708ms)
✔ WhatsApp consent is explicit, unchecked by default, and optional (3.8896ms)
✔ profile completion stores normalized phone and consent timestamp (0.724ms)
✔ profile completion refreshes the shared dashboard context before navigation (0.766ms)
✔ phone backfill changes only unambiguous Indian mobile formats (1.2198ms)
(node:35292) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/tenant/authorization.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ B2C remains an explicit non-institute tenant (17.2432ms)
✔ ABC CAT student receives CAT-only capabilities (1.7488ms)
✔ ABC CLAT and IPMAT students do not receive CAT capabilities (0.6241ms)
✔ wrong-institute and B2C profiles are denied on an institute hostname (0.8256ms)
✔ unknown hostnames fail closed (1.0967ms)
✔ missing institute branding uses safe Auctor assets and colors (3.5501ms)
✔ exam aliases normalize without defaulting unknown exams to CAT (0.5616ms)
✔ B2C active trial retains trial access (0.9921ms)
✔ B2C expired trial without subscription remains restricted (0.6367ms)
✔ B2C paid user retains premium access (0.815ms)
✔ institute CAT and CLAT students have full entitlement without a B2C subscription (0.7422ms)
✔ expired trial metadata never restricts an authorized institute student (0.378ms)
✔ null institute ID remains B2C and unauthenticated users have no entitlement (0.3962ms)
✔ hostname mismatch cannot grant institute entitlement (1.5512ms)
✔ exam capabilities remain independent from institute entitlement (0.6331ms)
(node:34252) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/lifecycle.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ lifecycle key is deterministic for the same trial (90.8464ms)
✔ signup scheduling excludes trial_day1 and uses configured offsets (1.3563ms)
✔ new trial enrollment creates exactly the six initial lifecycle event types (8.432ms)
✔ legacy and invalid trials are rejected (2.5587ms)
✔ automation is disabled unless explicitly true (0.9353ms)
✔ event payload and attempt validation rejects unsafe input (1.4341ms)
✔ cron processing requires the configured bearer secret (226.3084ms)
✔ migration enforces idempotency and claim eligibility (1.3717ms)
✔ migration excludes cancelled and sent events and recovers stale processing locks (1.015ms)
✔ completion RPCs fence every transition by claim token (1.2772ms)
✔ retry transitions are pending with bounded backoff, then permanently failed (110.8817ms)
✔ stale recovery clears ownership and excludes null or fresh locks (0.6712ms)
✔ unique lifecycle key and claim fencing model duplicate and old-worker protection (0.6615ms)
✔ migration keeps queue private and RPCs service-role only (0.5873ms)
✔ canonical trial activation enrolls through the existing welcome path (28.8701ms)
(node:40596) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/client.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ phone normalization preserves explicit international country codes (9.9939ms)
✔ all seven template definitions are separate and parameter-counted (0.6793ms)
✔ template builders reject missing values and validators reject wrong counts (1.8591ms)
✔ disabled and not-ready senders make zero requests (105.6809ms)
✔ missing Meta configuration and invalid phone fail before requesting (17.8865ms)
✔ test mode permits only the configured normalized recipient (122.1588ms)
✔ production queue processor does not claim lifecycle events in test mode (107.5423ms)
✔ enabled sender creates the correct Meta request and preserves message id (1.3105ms)
✔ Meta failures distinguish permanent and retryable categories (1.2662ms)
✔ network and timeout failures are retryable and never expose the token (61.8081ms)
✔ Meta error messages redact bearer credentials (1.1229ms)
✔ queue processor completes successful sends and retries transient failures (43.601ms)
✔ queue processor cancels purchased users without sending (1.0129ms)
✔ queue processor cancels users without consent and rechecks consent before Meta (2.7815ms)
✔ queue processor sends, retries transient failures, and cancels purchasers (3.4737ms)
✔ qualifying activity aggregates only supported question metrics (294.3122ms)
✔ non-question activity is real engagement but cannot create a misleading Day-1 (1.2484ms)
✔ no-session is cancelled for any qualifying activity and sent for zero activity (1.0345ms)
✔ final purchase check blocks a purchase occurring after claim (0.6247ms)
✔ first and subsequent activity summaries produce the same idempotent Day-1 identity (0.8103ms)
(node:40416) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/events/activity.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ missing profile is skipped without throwing and the handler still reaches claiming (224.0055ms)
✔ valid lifecycles after a missing profile reconcile before normal queue processing (8.3368ms)
✔ valid-user enrollment and processing are unchanged by a preceding missing profile (91.4357ms)
✔ actual profile database errors still abort instead of being silently skipped (7.0129ms)
(node:35028) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Projects/rc-mentor-ai/lib/whatsapp/webhook.js is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to C:\Projects\rc-mentor-ai\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Meta signature verification accepts only the matching raw-body HMAC (48.8236ms)
✔ parser extracts incoming text and status events (361.9061ms)
✔ unknown and irrelevant payloads are ignored safely (0.59ms)
✔ dispatcher isolates handler failures and continues other events (1.6655ms)
✔ message-event migration is private and duplicate-safe (1.0964ms)
ℹ tests 264
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 264
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 54266.4559
